{
    "subject": "resource/The_Craft_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "The Craft",
    "human_readable": "The name of the film is 'The Craft'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8300856947898865,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Craft'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8205450773239136,
            "question": "Is 'The Craft' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8101746439933777,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film 'The Craft' about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6260753273963928,
            "question": "Where was the film 'The Craft' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5778599381446838,
            "question": "When was the film 'The Craft' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5608896017074585,
            "question": "What genre might the film 'The Craft' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5484917163848877,
            "question": "What is the name of the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5266450643539429,
            "question": "Are there any sequels or spin-offs of the film 'The Craft'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4434761106967926,
            "question": "Has the film 'The Craft' received any awards or recognition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38552507758140564,
            "question": "Who are some of the main actors in 'The Craft'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of the film is 'The Craft'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6049_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has the film 'The Craft' received any awards or recognition?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6049_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any sequels or spin-offs of the film 'The Craft'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6049_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6049_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6049_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all three documents mention the title of the movie as \"The Craft\", making it true that the name of the film is indeed \"The Craft\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information in the provided documents supports the statement that \"The name of the film is 'The Craft'\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}